[
  {
    "options": ["Varšava", "Praha", "Berlín"],
    "question": "Hlavné mesto Polska?",
    "correctAnswer": "Varšava",
    "hint": ["Praha", "Varšava"]
  },
  {
    "options": ["Berlín", "Budapešť", "Bratislava"],
    "question": "Hlavné mesto Nemecka?",
    "correctAnswer": "Berlín",
    "hint": ["Berlín", "Budapešť"]
  },
  {
    "options": ["Helsinki", "Oslo", "Kyjev"],
    "question": "Hlavné mesto Fínska?",
    "correctAnswer": "Helsinki",
    "hint": ["Helsinki", "Oslo"]
  },
  {
    "options": ["Dublin", "Brusel", "Paríž"],
    "question": "Hlavné mesto Francúzska?",
    "correctAnswer": "Paríž",
    "hint": ["Dublin", "Paríž"]
  },
  {
    "options": ["Londýn", "Kodaň", "Monako"],
    "question": "Hlavné mesto Dánska?",
    "correctAnswer": "Kodaň",
    "hint": ["Monako", "Kodaň"]
  },
  {
    "options": ["Dublin", "Rím", "Luxemburg"],
    "question": "Hlavné mesto Írska?",
    "correctAnswer": "Dublin",
    "hint": ["Dublin", "Luxemburg"]
  },
  {
    "options": ["Barcelóna", "Lisabon", "Madrid"],
    "question": "Hlavné mesto Španielska?",
    "correctAnswer": "Madrid",
    "hint": ["Barcelóna", "Madrid"]
  },
  {
    "options": ["San Maríno", "Skopje", "Belehrad"],
    "question": "Hlavné mesto Srbska?",
    "correctAnswer": "Belehrad",
    "hint": ["Skopje", "Belehrad"]

  },
  {
    "options": ["Atény", "Podgorica", "Vilnius"],
    "question": "Hlavné mesto Grécka?",
    "correctAnswer": "Atény",
    "hint": ["Atény", "Vilnius"]
  },
  {
    "options": ["Bern", "Štokholm", "Sofia"],
    "question": "Hlavné mesto Bulharska?",
    "correctAnswer": "Sofia",
    "hint": ["Sofia", "Bern"]
  }
]
